A Guide to the Gregory-Whitmore Family Papers, 1846-1997 (bulk 1900-1923)
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Papers and Bound Volumes
  - Gregory Family Receipts and Photographs 1845-1866, n.d. (Box 5)
  - Scrapbook: Reunion of the Fifth Virginia Infantry and the 28th New York Volunteers, Niagara Falls 1883 (Box 5)
    Given as a memento to Samuel L. Whitmore by his mother, Susan Gregory Whitmore.
  - Samuel L. Whitmore to Harry Gregory Whitmore 1914-1915, Electrostatic copies (Box 5)
  - Travel Journal: Trip to California, Going thru the Panama Canal and Returning thru the Canadian Rockies, Volumes I & II, with related notes 1915 Jul-Aug, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Transcript: Trip to California, Going thru the Panama Canal and Returning thru the Canadian Rockies, Volumes I & II 1915 Jul-Aug (Box 5)
  - Diskettes with transcripts of Susan Gregory Whitmore's letters, 1900-1913, and "Trip to California...," 1915 1997, 4 diskettes (Box 5)